gamesthirst.com 2013-06-24

# Privacy Policy | Games Thirst – Video Game News, Reviews, Trailers, Wikis And The Official Gamer Drink

**Gamesthirst.com Â  Privacy policy**

Gamesthirst.com has created a privacy policy to show our strict commitment to the privacy of our users. The following makes plain information gathering and dissemination protocols for this website (Gamesthirst.com).

**Make Your Choice/You’re Not Obliged**

Gamesthirst.com gives users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving marketing and promotional information from us.

**Gathering of Information That’s Personal**

Personal Information is gathered based on the way users decide to interact with GamesThirst.com. Those who opt to register for GamesThirst.com will be asked to provide email address, and first and last name. Those who decide to participate in our online surveys will be asked to provide demographic information (like zip code, income level and age). Profile and Demographic data is also collected on GamesThirst.com. We use this information to make sure our users get the best experience possible on our site and to navigate them to what we believe they’ll be interested in, hence giving them an experience that fits their desires and preferences.

**Special Relationships/Protection of Personally-Identifying Information**

Because we use special relationships to improve our content, GamesThirst.com discloses personally identifying information to third party content and service providers. This decision is only based on the agreement that said service providers have agreed not to disclose the information to others. It they can’t assure that said information won’t be disclosed to other parties, then we won’t provide this information. Gamesthirst.com reserves the right to disclose potentially personally identifying information when required by law, or the rare circumstances when GamesThirst.com believes that disclosure is necessary to protect the property rights of the site, third parties, and the public.

**Staying Connected With Our Readership**

Occasionally, GamesThirst.com will send you email to keep you informed about upcoming events, new features, solicit your feedback and as the headline states, to stay connected with you. This will only happen if you are a registered member of GamesThirst.com and have supplied your email address. GamesThirst.com goes the full length to make sure our users are universally protected against unauthorized access, use, alteration or the destruction of potentially identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer and that the visitor’s browser provides the website each time the visitors comes back. The bottom line is computers are dumb, so programmers have to use cookies to keep track of information as you surf around. As a result websites become more dynamic. GamesThirst.com uses cookies to help the site track and identify users, how they use the site (GamesThirst.com) and their website access preferences. If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, you should set your browser to prevent cookies before using GamesThirst.com’s family of websites. If users choose to block cookies, they agree to the drawbacks of certain features of GamesThirst.com not functioning to the fullest potential.

**Links**

Gamesthirst.com contains external links to other sites. Gamesthirst.com is not responsible for the content on such sites and will not be held liable for the practices of such sites.

**Public Forums**

Gamesthirst.com makes forums, chat rooms, news groups, and message boards available to its users. Any information that is disclosed in those areas becomes public information. Remember to exercise caution before disclosing personal information.

**Contests**

We hold great contests on our site. Contact information of visitors will be requested (like email address) demographic information will also be requested (including zip code and, but not limited date of birth), information will be requested based upon contest being held.

**Changes:**

Gamesthirst.com will periodically make changes to its privacy policy. We encourage our users to check back on a regular basis to be informed on if any changes were made. If after changes occur you continue to use GamesThirst.com, such an action will automatically attest to your acceptance of the changes.

**Contact Gamesthirst.com  **

If you have any questions about the dealings and practices of this site, any question about this Privacy Policy, [contact us](http://www.gamesthirst.com/contact/ "Contact Us").
